And just when I was starting to like you!
我才刚刚开始喜欢上你啊
Don't make this harder than it is.
别搞得这么伤感啊
What the-- what's going on?
什么  现在是什么情况
You're throwing me out. You know, like you said you would.
你不是要把我赶出去吗 就像你说过的那样
Anne, truth be told,I was never gonna throw you out.
小安  说句实话 我从没想过赶你走
I was just talking tough so that you'd show me a little bit more respect.
我说话难听只是想让你对我放尊重点
That's kinda messed up, man.
您这么做可有点不地道  老爷子
Yeah. I probably was a little bit too harsh.
是啊  我可能有点太苛刻了
But I only did it because you remind me of myself when I was your age.
但我会这样做  是因为你让我回想起了我像你这么大的时候
Rough around the edges.
也是一样的不修边幅
Now, put that bag down, young lady. You're not going anywhere.
好了  把包放下吧  小姑娘 你哪里都不用去